TATIANE LEITE

SUMMARY OF **QUALIFICATIONS**

Eight years of experience in Computer Graphics.

Innovative and self-driven, with a patented idea in Brazil as result of a Master's degree.

Extremely versatile personality, transitions very well between different areas and enjoys to work in multi disciplinary environments.

> Spanish (intermediate); Portuguese (native).

SKILLS

Software: Maya, Photoshop, After Effects, Nuke, ZBrush, Avid, FinalCut, Adobe Premiere

Language: Java, Android, C, Python

ACHIEVEMENTS

Scholarship Mary Pickford 2016

Patent in Brazil 👓 Title: Improving the Attractiveness of Faces in Images Number: BR 10 2012 016227 0

Scholarship for Master's Program (2 years) - Sponsored by CAPES Foundation (Education Ministry of Brazil)

PUBLICATIONS

Graphics, Patterns and Images

Title: Improving the Attractiveness of Faces in Images 👓

Conference on Computer Graphics, Visualization and Computer Vision

Title: 3D Facial Animation for Mobile Devices 👓

WORK EXPERIENCE

7 Generation Games (CA, USA)

Jul 2016 - Now

General Artist 👓

- Worked on four shipped titles (3 for PCs, 1 for iPad)
- Collaborates closely with producer and developers to design game UI and art assets such as characters, backgrounds, icons, and promos, as well as adapting existing assets to different visual styles
- Creates appealing educational videos using a variety of compositing techniques, varying from exclusive 2D animations to mix of 2D elements over footage

In Transit Feature Film (CA, USA) Jul 2016 - Oct 2016

Editor 🖘

- Creatively assembled all the layers of images, music and dialogue in order to create a powerful narrative
- Collaborated closely with the director to understand the dramatic story line and build the rhythm, pace and tension desired for the scenes

Moonesta Short Film (CA, USA)

May 2016 - Jun 2016

- Came up with the easiest and fastest solution to create a VFX butterfly that would be a parody of a medical TV commercial
- Created a butterfly animation and composed it into the shots using techniques such as camera tracking, color correction, 3D layers and particles

UCLA Extension (CA, USA)

Jan 2013 - Dec 2013

Teaching Assistant

• Responsible for setting up and operating audiovisual equipments; maintain a record of every student's attendance and deliveries; organize and label all deliveries and plan schedules for presentations

Venturus Technical Innovation

Center (SP, Brazil) Oct 2008 - Jun 2010

Motorola (SP, Brazil)

Feb 2008 - Oct 2008

Software Engineer

• Developed apps that use camera phone and image processing to perform different activities such as panoramas pictures, face warp and face detection

Software Developer

•Tested, debugged and fixed mobile operating systems and new prototypes

EDUCATION

Santa Monica College (CA, USA)

University of Campinas (SP, Brazil)

UCLA Extension (CA, USA)

2015 - Present

Gnomon (CA, USA)

2014 - 2015

2012 - 2014

2010 - 2012

2003 - 2007

Animation Certificate

• GPA: 3.93

Visual Effects Courses

• Compositing, Digital Sculpting, Maya Courses such as Character Animation and Modeling

Certificate in Entertainment Studies

Earned with distinction

Master of Science in Computer Engineering ∞

• Thesis: Enhancement of facial attractiveness in images

University of Campinas (SP, Brazil) Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

SIBGRAPI 2015 - Conference on

WSCG10 - International

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

CTNx Creative Talent Network Animation Expo (Burbank, CA) 2015 and 2016

LABRFF Los Angeles Brazilian Film Festival (Los Angeles, CA) 2015 and 2016

Volunteer

 Organized and managed guest flow at venues; hosting and managing speakers, directing guests to correct lines and theaters

Volunteer

 Assisted the event director with day-to-day planning for festival events and screenings